<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recent on Brian Efflandt Coding Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://example.com/home/recent/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recent on Brian Efflandt Coding Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://example.com/home/recent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tic Tac Toe (React)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/home/recent/tictactoe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/home/recent/tictactoe/</guid>
      <description>For now, I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the React tutorial and added a method to highlight the winning column, and also enhanced the interface for a better look and feel.
I&amp;rsquo;m currently enrolled in a React.js course and intend to reiterate what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned from it here by ultimately componentizing this application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio Site (HUGO)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/home/recent/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/home/recent/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>Creating this site has been a big challenge, but I&amp;rsquo;ve learned volumes in the process. It&amp;rsquo;s given me more experience in all areas of SDLC, especially in the deployment and bug tracking area (organizing repositories and subdirectories with git, github, and gh-pages).
I found a theme that fit my eye for displaying my content the way I saw it in my mind and then went to work. All of the content menus and items were custom built by me, and honestly the only thing that remains of the original theme is the layout design to some extent&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expense Tracker (React)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/home/recent/expensetracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/home/recent/expensetracker/</guid>
      <description>React application which allows a user to input expenses and then has an interface for viewing and tracking the expenses from year to year.
This is my first project from a React.js course which offers a very thorough deep dive into React components. It requires peer reviews, has various quizzes and checkpoints, and in my opinion is teaching React in a way that challenges how I think and what I understand about javascript.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
